<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
    <id>org.getnevocoin.Nevocoin</id>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>BSD-3-Clause</project_license>
    <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
    <developer_name>The Monero Project</developer_name>
    <categories>
        <category>Network</category>
        <category>Qt</category>
        <category>Finance</category>
        <category>Office</category>
    </categories>
    <name>Nevocoin GUI</name>
    <summary>Nevocoin: the secure, private, untraceable cryptocurrency</summary>
    
    <description>
        <p>Nevocoin is a private, secure, untraceable, decentralised digital currency. You
            are your bank, you control your funds, and nobody can trace your transfers
            unless you allow them to do so.</p>

        <p>Privacy: Nevocoin uses a cryptographically sound system to allow you to send
            and receive funds without your transactions being easily revealed on the
            blockchain (the ledger of transactions that everyone has). This ensures that
            your purchases, receipts, and all transfers remain absolutely private by
            default.</p>

        <p>Security: Using the power of a distributed peer-to-peer consensus network,
            every transaction on the network is cryptographically secured. Individual
            wallets have a 25 word mnemonic seed that is only displayed once, and can be
            written down to backup the wallet. Wallet files are encrypted with a passphrase
            to ensure they are useless if stolen.</p>

        <p>Untraceability: By taking advantage of ring signatures, a special property of
            a certain type of cryptography, Nevocoin is able to ensure that transactions are
            not only untraceable, but have an optional measure of ambiguity that ensures
            that transactions cannot easily be tied back to an individual user or computer.</p>
    </description>

    <launchable type="desktop-id">org.getnevocoin.Nevocoin.desktop</launchable>

    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
            <caption>A screenshot of the Nevocoin GUI wallet</caption>
            <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/nevocoin/nevocoin-site/master/img/downloads/gui.png</image>
        </screenshot>
    </screenshots>

    <url type="homepage">https://nevocoin.org</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/nevocoin/nevocoin-gui/issues</url>
    <url type="donation">https://nevocoin.org/get-started/contributing</url>
    <url type="faq">https://nevocoin.org/get-started/faq</url>
    <url type="help">https://nevocoin.org/resources/user-guides</url>
    <url type="translate">https://translate.nevocoin.org</url>
    <url type="contact">https://nevocoin.org/community/hangouts</url>
    <url type="contribute">https://nevocoin.org/get-started/contributing</url>

    <releases>
        <release version="<version>" date="<date>"/>
    </releases>

    <custom>
      <value key="flathub::manifest">https://github.com/nevocoin/nevocoin-gui/tree/master/share/org.getnevocoin.Nevocoin.yaml</value>
    </custom>
</component>
